Stephanie Giel

410 W. Desert Flower Ln, Phoenix, AZ 85045 • (602) 292-2528 stephaniegiel@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Office Administrator with experience in managing data, implementing and running a website, facilitating communications among groups, coordinating weekly volunteers, and managing facility space, including rentals and maintenance. Self-driven and proactive in assuming new responsibilities as needed due to limited staff.

EDUCATION

- Arizona State University, Masters in Information Systems (emphasis Statistical Data Analysis), Dec. 1989
- Arizona State University, Bachelor in Mathematics, Dec. 1988

EXPERIENCE

Wveth Averst Research. Clinical Pharmacokineticist 1990 – 2012 (1990-1993, employed in-house; 1993-2012 employed full-time as a consultant)

- Worked as statistician in a Clinical Pharmacokinetics group.
- Collaborated on team projects
- Performed the pharmacokinetic data analysis, statistical programming and writing of scientific reports to be submitted to the FDA.
- Wrote automated programs to be shared with other Pharmacokineticists on my team to perform routine pharmacokinetic data analyses

Desert Foothills United Methodist Church, Office Administrator 2012 - Current

- Implemented and manage church database using ShelbyNext.
- Manage building use by members and community including rentals of space to music teachers, AA groups, Boy Scouts, Maricopa County Elections.
- Implemented and manage church website, www.desertfoothills.org
- Manage all church communications including weekly emails and quarterly newsletters
- Manage and coordinate weekly volunteers
- Facilitate communication between staff, volunteers and members
- Troubleshoot and resolve office equipment issues to minimize service visit costs
- Manage vendor relationships

SKILLS

- Microsoft Word, Excel, Microsoft Publisher, Google Docs and Google Sheets
- Proactive in anticipating needs and adjusting job responsibilities as necessary